[Music] that's it that's it
[Música]
either Just one
que ya está que tampoco Solo una
more question but on a friend level eh I
pregunta más pero a nivel amigo eh No te
'm not interviewing you Why do you think she
estoy entrevistando Por qué crees que no
hasn't responded She hasn't made any
ha respondido ella no ha hecho ningún
kind of allusion response because
tipo de alusión respuesta porque a mí
for example she told me if there's something that does
por ejemplo ella me dijo si hay algo que
n't fit or I don't like I'll put some
no me cuadra o no me gusta pondré unas
stories or the same she even sent an
historias o lo mismo incluso mando un
audio she told me I had
audio me dijo
her capable of that night
yo la había capaz de que esa noche
entering into what I expected because she
entraba en lo que yo esperaba porque
thinks that in the end no
cree que al final no
Why do you think that in the end no well
Por qué crees que al final no pues
because maybe I think that maybe it's that
porque a lo mejor yo creo que a lo mejor
this is speculation
es que no los esto es una especulación
you have asked me why do you think I think
tú me has preguntado por qué crees Yo
that Antonio David must have told her not to
creo que Antonio David le habrá dicho no
get into controversies because we are not
te metas en polémicas porque tampoco nos
interested in getting into this specific one
interesa meternos ahí en esta concreta
with Marina or I mean I don't know do you
con Marina o sea no sé
understand
lo entiendes
Yes but you know how she is that there is
Sí pero tú sabes cómo es ella que ella
no one who can stop her many times
no hay quien la frene muchas veces
the other can tell her mass and she such
el otro le puede decir misa y ella tal
I expected at least something but I
yo me esperaba aunque fuera algo pero yo
already said that she had looked for herself I already
ya dije que se había buscado yo ya le
told her that she had looked for the
dije a ella que se había buscado un
wrong enemy but it's an
enemigo equivocado pero es que un
enemy that I do not consider myself her
enemigo que yo no me considero su
enemy she is the one who  you saw it that way
enemiga ella es la que lo ha visto así
then I already told you that it was
entonces yo ya le dije que era
wrong and you were wrong and so much so that's it,
equivocado y se ha equivocado y tanto
if your attitude is
que bueno ya está pues si su actitud es
silence, mine too, I mean I
el silencio la mía también o sea yo
told that and mine will continue to be
conté eso y la mía va a seguir siendo el
silence if she, I repeat, gets married or
silencio si ella repito se casa o
announces that she's getting married, well we'll comment on it
anuncia que se casa pues lo comentaremos
here or she announces that she's returning to work,
aquí o anuncia que vuelve al trabajo
well we'll also have to comment on it or she
pues también habrá que comentarlo o
announces
anuncia
that she's pregnant. Well also, I mean I have
que está embarazada Pues también o sea
to say but no more on this subject
tengo que decir pero ya más de este tema
because there's also nothing else to
no porque es que tampoco hay más que
comment on. I mean if you told me that they or
comentar O sea si me dijeras que ellos o
Antonio Navización directly and gives some
Antonio navización directo y da algún
kind of information on the matter that he
tipo de información al respecto que no
hasn't spoken about either or says something, well that's it. Well maybe
se ha pronunciado tampoco o dice algo
Marta has
pues ya está Pues a lo mejor Marta ha
reflected on this subject,
reflexionado respecto a este tema no lo
I don't know, I don't know anything about her, in fact I have
sé yo no sé nada de ella de hecho es que
her blocked on WhatsApp. Well
la tengo bloqueada en el WhatsApp no
basically, Well that's it
Pues básicamente
Marina,
Bueno pues ya está Marina
but I'm very happy and delighted that
pero estoy muy contento y encantado de
you're here again in your house,
que estés aquí otra vez en tu casa
little house.
casita
[Music]
[Música]